DMI City Weather provides local weather information from the Danish Meteorological Institute, based on your current location.

(Partial content of this app is always in Danish.)

DMI Byvejr viser dig lokal vejrudsigt fra Dansk Dansk Meteorologisk Institut, baseret på din nuværende position.

This update includes:

* Support for Greenland and Faroe Islands
* Beach Weather
* Radar images for rain, snow and lightning
* Minor adjustments and performance improvements

---

Byvejret fra DMI

---

dmi, weather, byvejr, vejr, vejret
